Guide to the UE Local 610 Records, 1937-1990 UE.16.610
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE Local 610 Records
1937-1990
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. Local 610 (Wilmerding, Pa.)
UE.16.610
60.94 Linear Feet (39 boxes)
The UE Local 610 operated from 1937 to the present at Westinghouse Airbrake Company's Airbrake Division in Wilmerding, Pennsylvania, and its Union Switch and Signal Division in Swissvale, Pennsylvania. Local 610 represents workers in these plants for purposes of collective bargaining and for the adjustment of grievances arising from contract and shop floor disputes. Files date from 1937 to 1990 and include correspondence, meeting minutes, publications, grievance files, arbitrations, newspaper clippings, and subject files.
History
In 1881, George Westinghouse established the Union Switch and Signal plant in Swissvale, Pennsylvania, and in 1889 he moved his airbrake manufacturing facility to nearby Wilmerding, Pennsylvania. In both facilities, Westinghouse instituted company welfare programs advocated by other industrialists of the day. The Depression of the 1930's forced the company to abandon its high wage and benefits program, thus encouraging labor organization. The affiliation of the Westinghouse Electric workers in East Pittsburgh with the United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE) as UE Local 601 encouraged the Wilmerding workers to organize with UE, and in May 1937, the UE chartered the Wilmerding union as Local 610. In November of the same year, a National Labor Relations Board election was held and the union was approved. In theory, UE Local 610 thereby became the exclusive bargaining agent for production and maintenance workers at the Wilmerding plant. However, it took three years and a favorable Supreme Court ruling in a related case before the company conceded a written contract to the union. Also in 1941, the Local won bargaining rights at the Switch and Signal Division in Swissvale, bringing the Local's numbers to approximately 6,500 workers.
Although major strikes occurred throughout Westinghouse Electric plants in 1946, Local 610 successfully negotiated wage increases without striking. Through the use of the court system, the Local avoided strikes and ensured returning World War II veterans paid vacations the year they resumed work. The Local also secured a favorable ruling from the Pennsylvania Unemployment Compensation Bureau in 1950 which granted retiring workers compensation they had previously been denied. An anniversary article in the UE News in 1957 reprised such UE Local 610 negotiating successes as its elimination of gender-based wage differentials and its guarantees of transfers based on seniority. The Local also adopted annual secret ballot elections for officers and stewards. In the early 1960s, the Local engaged in arbitration with the company to protect women from compulsory retirement. Similarly, the Local sought to obtain cost of living adjustments, equal employment opportunities, and improved levels of occupational safety for its workers.
In 1950 and again in 1953, a rival union, the International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (IUE), unsuccessfully challenged the bargaining rights of UE Local 610. During this time Local 610 president Harold Briney and at least one other Local member faced accusations of communist activity; however, attempts by rival unions, including the International Association of Machinists, United Steelworkers of America, United Auto Workers, and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, to raid the Local's members in the 1950's also failed.
In 1968 American Standard purchased both the Swissvale and Wilmerding facilities, and the Local's first strike occurred in 1969 to induce contract negotiations. Another strike occurred in 1978 after the expiration of the contract. The Local's longest strike began November 1, 1981 when approximately 3,700 workers walked off the job after the expiration of their three-year contract. The strike, which focused on productivity and salary issues, continued for two hundred and five days during which the legality of mass picketing and non-union workers performing assembly line work were contested. In May 1982, the membership rejected a tentative agreement that did not include the reinstatement of twenty-two workers accused of strike-related violence and vandalism. However, the contract was settled by the end of the month.
On August 20, 1982 the company served notice of the transfer of approximately one hundred and fifty jobs from the wiring department of the Swissvale plant to Macon, Georgia. In addition, the company began to transfer several other jobs to areas of the Southern United States such as Batesburg, South Carolina. In response, the "Save Our Switch Coalition" produced petitions, wrote to politicians, and publicized the plight of the workers. In 1986, Local 610 faced an even more serious threat of job losses when the company announced its intent to remove work to other areas and close the Wilmerding and Swissvale plants. These actions spurred the Local to establish a nonprofit organization entitled "Coalition to Save the Brake and Switch." The Coalition engaged in a card campaign to the company president, leafleted the surrounding neighborhood, and lobbied local politicians, government and economic organizations to stop the removal of work. Despite these efforts, the Swissvale plant closed and the Wilmerding workforce was greatly diminished. In an attempt to alleviate the financial burdens of its membership, the Local shifted its priorities to utilizing the 1974 Trade Adjustment Act (TRA/TAA) to acquire job training and severance pay for its terminated workers.
Scope and Content Notes
This subgroup includes correspondence, meeting minutes, publications, grievance files, arbitrations, newspaper clippings, and subject files. Files are arranged alphabetically unless specified otherwise. The records in this subgroup have been divided into sixteen series and more specific information can be found in the series scope notes
Arrangement
Series 16.610.1. Minutes
Series 16.610.2. National Labor Relations Board Cases
Series 16.610.3. Correspondence
Series 16.610.4. Contracts and Negotiations
Series 16.610.5. Health, Insurance, and Pension Plans
Series 16.610.6. Grievances
Series 16.610.7. Arbitrations
Series 16.610.8. Publications
Series 16.610.9. Subject Files
Series 16.610.10. Taft-Hartley Compliance
Series 16.610.11. 1981-1982 Strike
Series 16.610.12. Coalition to Save
Series 16.610.13. Trade Adjustment Act (TRA) and Severance Pay
Series 16.610.14. Membership Cards
Series 16.610.15. Job Descriptions and Rate Changes
Series 16.610.16. Layoff, Recall, Seniority, Termination, and Transfer Lists
Access Restrictions
Records of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America are closed for a period of twenty-five years after their creation. Access to Boxes 16 and 20 requires a signed confidentiality agreement.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, Local 610 in 1989. Additional materials were donated by Ed Huot in 1998.
Previous Citation
UE Local 610 Records, 1937-1990, UE.16.610, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE) Local 610, Records, 1937-90, UE:LOCAL610, Archives Service Center, University Library System, University of Pittsburgh
Related Material
Charles J. McCollester Collection on the 1981-82 Electrical Workers Strike at Westinghouse Airbrake Company (Wilmerding, Pa. and Swissvale, Pa.), 1981-83, AIS.1988.18, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Robert Jurich Scrapbooks, 1981-1990, AIS.1990.15, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE District 6 Records, 1940s-1980s, UE.15.6, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE News Photograph Collection, 1933-1998, UE.14.1, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE National Office Records Relating to District 6 and District 6 Locals, 1936-1990s, UE.4.1.6, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Officials and employees; Labor union meetings -- Pennsylvania; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- History; Industries -- Pennsylvania -- Wilmerding; Industries -- Pennsylvania -- Swissvale; Labor unions -- Organizing -- Pennsylvania; Labor; Labor unions -- Pennyslvania -- History -- 20th century; Women labor union members -- Pennsylvania; Women electric industry workers -- Pennsylvania; Seeger, Pete; Union Switch and Signal Company; Westinghouse Air Brake Company; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America -- History; American Standard, inc.; Briney, Harold; Save Our Switch Coalition
- Minutes, 1942-1985; 16.610.1.
  Scope and Contents note
  The materials in this series are arranged alphabetically by folder title and date from 1941 to 1985. While the bulk of the executive board minutes relate to donations to the community, they also include resolutions endorsed by the Local on topics related to World War II and communist investigations. Membership meeting minutes contain the business agent's report, recommendations from the executive board, discussions on special topics and the nominations of delegates to conventions, the executive board, and other panels. Steward meetings provide information on the more pertinent worker issues such as dues increases, layoffs, grievances and collecting funds. This series also contains a file on the 1981 organizing of salaried workers.
  - Executive Board, 1942-1974 (Box 1, Folder 01-08)
  - Membership Meetings, 1941-1971 (Box 1, Folder 09-13)
  - Miscellaneous: Switch, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
  - Salaried Workers Organizing Committee, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Steward Meetings: Airbrake Division, 1959-1972 (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
  - Steward Meetings: Union Switch and Signal, 1950-1985 (Box 1, Folder 19-21)
  - Union Office, 1964-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- National Labor Relations Board Cases, 1937-1959; 16.610.2.
  These materials are arranged chronologically and date from 1937 thru the 1960s. Files exist for Local 610's petitions and elections for representation at the Wilmerding and Swissvale plants. This series also includes representation petitions and elections from other unions such as the International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (IUE), and Patternmakers League. Additional files relate to unfair labor practices charges filed against the company and the Local during the 1950s for collective bargaining and representation rights.
  - UE: Wilmerding, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - UE: Swissvale, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 02-03)
  - Swissvale: Watchmen and Patrolmen, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Die Sinkers v. UE, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - IUE v UE, 1949-1953 (Box 2, Folder 06-08)
  - Patternmakers League v. UE, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 09-11)
  - IBEW v. UE, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Unfair Labor Practices: Collective Bargaining, 1938-1940 (Box 2, Folder 13-14)
  - Unfair Labor Practices: Filed by IBEW against UE, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Unfair Labor Practices: Filed by Individuals against UE, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Government Pamphlets on Labor Laws, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1939-1948; 16.610.3.
  This series relates directly to the National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) and arbitration files from 1939 to 1948. Files regarding Executive Order 9240 document overtime issues. NLRB/Arbitrations files contain correspondence with union officials and legal representatives on the progress of arbitration proceedings. Files entitled "Company Officials" contain information on contract negotiations and the arbitration of grievances.
  - Executive Order 9240, 1942-1944 (Box 2, Folder 18-20)
  - NLRB/Arbitration, 1941-1948 (Box 2, Folder 20-41)
  - Negotiations: Airbrake Division, 1939-1945 (Box 2, Folder 42-46)
  - Officials: Airbrake Division, 1940-1948 (Box 2, Folder 47-55)
  - Officials: Switch Division, 1941-1947 (Box 2, Folder 56-63)
- Contracts and Negotiations, 1941-1988; 16.610.4.
  This series contains contract agreements reached between Local 610 and the Westinghouse Airbrake Company, which are arranged chronologically. In addition to the major contract agreements, these files also contain supplemental agreements on specific issues, such as wage increases, pension, and benefit plans; supporting materials collected for negotiations; negotiation minutes; and company and union proposals. This series also includes agreements from other companies and locals/unions in related industries.
  - Agreement: Switch, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Agreement: Switch, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Agreement: WABCO, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Agreement: Watchmen and Patrolmen, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Agreement: NWLB Interim Directive, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Proposals: Switch, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Extension of 1943 Contract, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Agreement: WABCO, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Agreement: WABCO, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Agreement: WABCO - Wage Increase, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Negotiations: Minutes, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Agreement with Proposals and Counters, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Supporting Material, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Negotiations: Minutes, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Agreement: Veteran's Vacation, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Negotiations: Minutes, 1949-1951 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Agreement: Airbrake, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Agreement: Switch, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Union Proposals, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Agreement: Airbrake, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Agreement: Switch, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Negotiations: Minutes, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Proposals, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 23-24)
  - Supporting Materials, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Agreement: Switch, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Agreement: WABCO, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Agreement: Switch, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Agreement: Switch, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Agreement: Switch - Seniority, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Agreement: Switch, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Agreement: WABCO, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Agreement: Switch Wage Rates, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Contract and Insurance, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Negotiations: Minutes - Airbrake, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Negotiations: Minutes - Airbrake, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 01-02)
  - Agreement: Signal and Communications Division, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Agreement: WABCO, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Agreement: Switch, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Negotiations: Minutes - WABCO, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 06-07)
  - Agreement: WABCO, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Negotiations: Minutes - WABCO, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 09-10)
  - Signed Supplemental Agreements: Switch, 1961-1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Supplemental Agreements: WABCO, 1980-1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Union Proposals, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Negotiations: Salaried Workers - Airbrake, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Agreement: WABCO, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Memorandum on Settlement, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Agreements: Switch, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Agreement: Base Rates - Airbrake, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Company Proposals, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Supplemental Agreements, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Union Proposals: Supplemental Agreements, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Contract Survey, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 22-24)
  - Contract Survey, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 01-03)
  - Agreement: WABCO, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Contract Proposals, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Negotiations: General, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Negotiations: Ed Huot's Personal Notes, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Negotiations: Leaflets, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Negotiations: Minutes, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Negotiations: Opening Statements, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Memorandum of Settlement: Airbrake, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - American Standard: Contracts with other organizations, 1965-1970 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Outside Agreements, 1955-1979 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Other UE Locals, 1966-1971 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - General Electric and UE, 1973-1978 (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
  - United Auto Workers, 1970, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - United Steel Workers, 1962-1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - United Steel Workers, Pension, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - WABCO and UE, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Westinghouse Electric and IUE, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Westinghouse Electric and UE, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Health, Insurance and Pension Plans, 1945-1989; 16.610.5.
  Extensive files exist for health plans considered by and utilized by the Local, such as Health America. This series also contains general information and settlement files for pension plans and the weekly indemnity insurance program, which relate to the contract and negotiations files.
  - Benefits Changes, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Health Plans: Active, 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 02-03)
  - Health Plans: Blue Cross/ Blue Shield, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Health Plans: Forbes Health Maintenance Plan, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Health Plans: General Information, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Health Plans: Health America, 1984-1989 (Box 6, Folder 07-09)
  - Health Plans: US Healthcare, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Insurance Plans: 1945 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Insurance Plans: 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Insurance Plans: 1975 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Insurance Plans: 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Medical Bills, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Pension: Benefit Information, 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Pension: D 2 Compliance, 1964-1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Pension: General Information, 1959-1973 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Pension: Increases for Retirees, 1973-1978 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Pension: Information for Terminated Employees, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Pension: Negotiations, 1959-1972 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Pension: Settlements, 1959-1983 (Box 6, Folder 22-25)
  - Pension: Vision Plan, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Weekly Indemnity Insurance Program: General Information, 1961-1972 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Weekly Indemnity Insurance Program: Settlements, 1969-1978 (Box 6, Folder 28-30)
- Grievances, 1942-1988; 16.610.6.
  Access Restrictions
  Access to Box 16, Folders 2, 37 and 38 requires a signed confidentiality agreement.
  These files contain minutes from the grievance meetings, as well as the grievances themselves. The meeting minutes are divided into those originating from the Airbrake Division and those from the Switch and Signal Division. The minutes include the date of the meeting, representatives from the company and the union, the grievance to be discussed, and the parties' main arguments. The grievances are arranged by department for 1943 to 1955, section for 1955 to 1986 or alphabetically by either complainant or topic for the 1970 to 1980s. The grievances reveal the date, department, and nature of the grievance.
  - Minutes: Airbrake, 1942-1974 (Box 7, Folder 01-27)
  - Minutes: Switch, 1947-1973 (Box 8, Folder 01-17)
  - Minutes: Switch, 1974-1980 (Box 9, Folder 01-15)
  - Minutes: Switch, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 01-07)
  - Insurance, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Salary Workers, 1967-1980 (Box 10, Folder 9-15)
  - Section 220, 1971-1977 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Grievances: Department A, 1943-1954 (Box 11, Folder 01-03)
  - Grievances: Department AB, 1943-1953 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Grievances: Department AC, 1944-1954 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Grievances: Department AUT, 1943-1954 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Grievances: Department B, 1945-1953 (Box 11, Folder 7-10)
  - Grievances: Department C, 1943-1955 (Box 11, Folder 11-13)
  - Grievances: Department CD, 1944-1955 (Box 11, Folder 14-15)
  - Grievances: Department CP, 1947-1954 (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
  - Grievances: Department CP, 1943-1946 (Box 12, Folder 01-02)
  - Grievances: Department D, 1943-1952 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Grievances: Department DA, 1949-1953 (Box 12, Folder 04-06)
  - Grievances: Department DC, 1944-1955 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Grievances: Department DM, 1943-1953 (Box 12, Folder 08-09)
  - Grievances: Department E, 1943-1953 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Grievances: Department F, 1944-1948 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Grievances: Department G, 1943-1955 (Box 12, Folder 12-16)
  - Grievances: Department GAGE, 1943-1953 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Grievances: Department H, 1943-1953 (Box 12, Folder 18-19)
  - Grievances: Department I, 1945-1954 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Grievances: Department JJ - Coreroom, 1943-1954 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Grievances: Department JJ - Foundry, 1943-1954 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Grievances: Department K, 1946-1954 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Grievances: Department L, 1947-1950 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Grievances: Department NN, 1944-1953 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Grievances: Department O, 1943-1952 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Grievances: Department Q, 1943-1954 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Grievances: Department R, 1943-1954 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Grievances: Department Reservoir, 1943-1953 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Grievances: Department S, 1943-1955 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Grievances: Department SS, 1946-1955 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Grievances: Department T, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Grievances: Department U, 1943-1955 (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
  - Grievances: Department Y, 1945-1953 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Grievances: Department Z, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Grievances: Holiday, 1947-1948 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Grievances: Miscellaneous, 1942-1947 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Grievances: Pending, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Grievances: Plant-Wide, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Grievances: Verbal, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Grievances: Section 1-2, 1954-1983 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Grievances: Section 2, 1954-1984 (Box 14, Folder 03-06)
  - Grievances: Section 2 - Verbal, 1975-1980 (Box 14, Folder 07-08)
  - Grievances: Section 3, 1954-1959 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Grievances: Section 4, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Grievances: Section 5, 1967-1979 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Grievances: Section 6, 1977-1985 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Grievances: Section 7, 1959-1978 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Grievances: Section 8, 1954-1981 (Box 14, Folder 14-15)
  - Grievances: Section 9, 1955-1985 (Box 14, Folder 16-17)
  - Grievances: Section 9 - Verbal, 1963-1965 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Grievances: Section 10, 1956-1965 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Grievances: Section Coreroom, 1955-1985 (Box 14, Folder 20-21)
  - Grievances: Section Foundry, 1955-1984 (Box 14, Folder 22-23)
  - Grievances: Section 12, 1955-1971 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Grievances: Section 15, 1955-1979 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Grievances: Section 20, 1958-1977 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Grievances: Section 21, 1955-1983 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Grievances: Section 22, 1965-1983 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Grievances: Section 23, 1954-1958 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Grievances: Section 24, 1954-1978 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Grievances: Section 25, 1951-1984 (Box 15, Folder 03-04)
  - Grievances: Section 26, 1955-1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Grievances: Section 27, 1953-1960 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Grievances: Section 28, 1956-1966 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Grievances: Section 31, 1954-1964 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Grievances: Section 35, 1955-1960 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Grievances: Section 43, 1954-1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Grievances: Section 45, 1955-1985 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Grievances: Section 52, 1954-1980 (Box 15, Folder 12-13)
  - Grievances: Section 53, 1978-1982 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Grievances: Section 57, 1953-1965 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Grievances: Section 58, 1955-1958 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Grievances: Section 62, 1965-1980 (Box 15, Folder 17)